fashionone.com 2019-07-23

# Privacy Policy - Fashion One

### **Introduction**

We understand your concern about how your personal data is used and protected.  
This Privacy Policy explains how we use and protect the personal data collected on this website.   
This Policy explains which personal data is collected by FASHION ONE (FASHOIN ONE LLC, hereby mentioned as “FASHION ONE” or “we”). We want to make sure that we are fully transparent regarding how your data is used.

This Privacy Policy applies to your use of our website, its tools and any related services.   
We reserve ourselves the right to change this Policy at any time without notice, so please check it regularly.  
Our Policy applies to all visitors, users and others who access the Service (“Users”).

Please read the Privacy Policy carefully and contact us with any questions or concerns about our privacy practices.

### **Who are we?**

This website’s information is controlled by FASHION ONE LLC, a commercial company registered in State of Delaware under the fiscal number 27-4166627. Its head office is located at: 246 West Broadway New York NY 10013.  
The Marketing Department is in charge of our data protection management and can be contacted via the following email: DataProtection@fashionone.com

### **How do we collect personal data?**

This Policy applies to Personal Data that we collect from or about you, through the methods described below, from the following sources:

**FASHION ONE websites.** Consumer-directed websites operated by or for FASHION ONE, including sites that we operate under our own domains/URLs and mini-sites that we run on third party social networks such as Facebook (“Websites”).

**Offline registration forms.** Printed or digital registration and similar forms that we collect via, for example, postal mail, in-store demos, contests and other promotions, or events.

### **What data do we collect?**

We collect the following personal data:

  * Name;
  * Email address,

### **How do we use personal Data?**

Personal data is gathered as you fill in the subscription for the FASHION ONE newsletter for marketing purposes (such as the delivery of the newsletter and information about contests), improving and developing new programs and services. 

We also use your Personal Data for consumer service purposes, including responding to your enquiries. This typically requires the use of certain personal contact information and information regarding the reason for your inquiry (e.g. order status, technical issue, product question/complaint, general question, etc.)

### **What legal basis do we have for collection and processing your personal data?**

The collection of your personal data is based on your explicit consent on a well-informed basis. We collect your personal data for fulfilling our contractual obligations, our legitimate interests and our other legal obligations. As you know you may always unsubscribe your explicit consent. 

### **When do we share personal data?**

Your data is confidential and therefore not shared except for FASHION ONE entities and FASHION ONE’s business partners in association with your relationship with FASHION ONE. Other than this, we only share your data with third parties when we are required to do so by law.

### **Where do we store and process personal data?**

Your Personal Data is collected and stored in a database by Mailchimp of the Rocket Science Group (Subcontractor), who abides by the obligations established in the Article 28 of the GDPR. 

All personal data is encrypted through a SSL security certificate. Therefore, the collected data is handled only by FASHION ONE.

FASHION ONE and Subcontractor proceed to the permanent monitoring of access to the information technology systems in order to prevent, detect and stop unauthorized use of your personal data.

### **How do we secure personal data?**

We carry out the activities necessary to ensure the security of your personal data and takes all technical and administrative measures necessary to conform to the legal requirements and adequate measures required by the GDPR to ensure legal processing of this data.

### **How long do we keep your personal data for?**

We keep your personal data until 

  * any applicable limitation period (i.e. any period during which a person could bring a legal claim against us), and
  * if any relevant legal claims are brought, we may continue to process your Personal Data for such additional time necessary in connection with that claim.

During the periods noted above, we will restrict our processing of your Personal Data to storage or, and maintaining the security of those data, except to the extent the data need to be reviewed in connection with any claim, or any obligation under applicable law.

After above mentioned periods, we are permanently going to delete or destroy the relevant Personal Data or anonymize the relevant Personal Data.

### **Your rights regarding your personal data**

We respect your rights to access and control your personal data.  In accordance with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016, you have the right to access, review and request a physical or electronic copy of data held about you. You also have the right to request information on the source of your Personal Data. You can (i) request deletion, the portability, correction or revision of your Personal Data; (ii) limit the use and disclosure of your Personal Data; and (iii) revoke consent to any of our data processing activities.

Please note that, in certain circumstances, we will not be able to delete your personal data. We may be required to retain some of your Personal Data after you have requested deletion, to satisfy our legal or contractual obligations. We may also be permitted by applicable laws to retain some of your Personal Data to satisfy our business needs.

You also have the right to object, on grounds relating to your particular situation, to the use of your relevant personal data by us, or on our behalf; and the right to object to the processing of your relevant personal data by us, or on our behalf, for direct marketing purposes.

These rights can be exercised by sending us an e-mail [DataProtection@fashionone.com](mailto:DataProtection@fashionone.com) or writing to us at Data Protection Fashion One, 246 West Broadway New York NY 10013, attaching a copy of your ID or equivalent details (where requested by us and permitted by law). If the request is submitted by a person other than you, without providing evidence that the request is legitimately made on your behalf, the request will be rejected. Please note that any identification information provided to us will only be processed in accordance with, and to the extent permitted by applicable laws.

We hope that We can satisfy queries you may have about the way we process your Personal Data. However, if you have unresolved concerns you also have the right to complain to competent data protection authorities.

### **How to contact us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us via the following channels:

Address:   
FASHION ONE LLC.   
246 West Broadway  
New York NY 10013

Email: DataProtection@fashionone.com

### **Use of cookies and other technologies**

We use a technology called cookies. A cookie is a small data file that is stored in your computer or mobile web browser in order to collect relevant data. The cookies we use tell us your search preferences, various user preferences you have set and which pages you have visited. This way, it allows us to provide you with additional functionalities and helps us analyse website usage more accurately.  
Unless you have adjusted your browser settings so that it refuses cookies, we will drop cookies onto your computer when you visit our website.  
Additionally, you might be exposed to cookies provided by third parties, such as Facebook, Google and other third-party service providers associated with this website. FASHION ONE cannot be held responsible for how these third-party cookies are used and you should consult the Privacy Policies of these third parties for more information about how they use cookies.

For more information about cookies, [contact us](http://www.fashionone.com/contact/).
